{
    "questions": [
        {
            "questionNo": "1",
            "question": "Q1. What is capital of India?",
            "ans": "Delhi",
            "options": [
                "Newwork",
                "Delhi",
                "Chenai",
                "Mumbai"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNo": "2",
            "question": "Q2. What is capital of Punjab?",
            "ans": "Chandigarh",
            "options": [
                "Bangalore",
                "Delhi",
                "Kolkata",
                "Chandigarh"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNo": "3",
            "question": "Q3. What is capital of West Bangal?",
            "ans": "Kolkata",
            "options": [
                "Bangalore",
                "Delhi",
                "Kolkata",
                "Chandigarh"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNo": "4",
            "question": "Q4. What is capital of Goa?",
            "ans": "Panji",
            "options": [
                "Bangalore",                
                "Kolkata",
                "Panji",
                "Chandigarh"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNo": "5",
            "question": "Q5. What is capital of Karnatka?",
            "ans": "Bangalore",
            "options": [                
                "Kolkata",
                "Bangalore",
                "Delhi",
                "Chandigarh"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNo": "6",
            "question": "Q6. What is capital of Bihar?",
            "ans": "Patna",
            "options": [                
                "Patna",
                "Bangalore",
                "Delhi",
                "Bhopal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNo": "7",
            "question": "Q7. What is capital of Maharastra?",
            "ans": "Mumbai",
            "options": [                
                "Patna",
                "Bangalore",
                "Delhi",
                "Mumbai"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNo": "8",
            "question": "Q8. What is capital of Tamilnadu?",
            "ans": "Chenai",
            "options": [                
                "Kolkata",
                "Bangalore",
                "Chennai",
                "Bhopal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNo": "9",
            "question": "Q9. What is capital of Assam?",
            "ans": "Dispur",
            "options": [                
                "Patna",
                "Dispur",
                "Delhi",
                "Bhopal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "questionNo": "10",
            "question": "Q10. What is capital of Jharkhand?",
            "ans": "Ranchi",
            "options": [                
                "Patna",
                "Ranchi",
                "Delhi",
                "Mumbai"
            ]
        }
    ]
}